sup everyone cameras 1 2 3 4 5 here with
a very special video today now I just
got back from while I'm out where I saw
something that really shocked my ass
like you you all know the Teletubbies
right you know that that baby [ __ ] from
like all the way back then well uphills
Lee had a [ __ ] reboot with some [ __ ]
were they brought like babies like look
I don't know what the [ __ ] that is all
about but they were like a bunch of like
different called babies like baby
Teletubbies called the kid Lee Tommy's
know at first I thought ok maybe they
want to get more into the baby
demographic or some [ __ ] like that
although the closer I looked at I
thought wait no is this a ripoff or sock
on the ground look at first like I know
that sounds crazy but if you look look
at the color scheme of the babies they
match perfectly with the sock
Underground Cariocas that I use for my
youtube channel
yeah I'll show you like out like that
sounds crazy I know but but it's the
[ __ ] they're called the tippy-toe
tippy-toe B's I want to do a little
investigation we are gonna go to the
wiki cuz there is some stuff on talk
about like all off spoil some [ __ ] there
is a blue one and a yellow one oh yes
just like soccer Bobby who are blue and
yellow these two are like gasps [ __ ]
now we'll go here we'll go wake you on
I'll show you what the [ __ ] what the
[ __ ] I'm talking about this is here we
go TV tubby Zwicky right here
Teletubbies da wiki now this is just
another thing I noticed one thing is
look right here as you can see on the
website
um beep um B that's the yellow one that
this one is clearly based on Bobby yeah
I'll try to find a picture with all the
colors let me just scroll down a bit see
what I can uncover cuz this is hurt here
I see them okay
though right there the the [ __ ]
babies let's see if I can follow with
all that look look look at that first of
all look at this right here we can see
here are four of them Sleeting like as
you can see this one's blue like Sonic
the Hedgehog pink like Sonia the
Hedgehog green like magnetic and y'all
like Barbie look you can make that up
these are my character designs like I'm
sorry and yes I'm calling sock
Underground mine B I technically own it
now everybody knows that [ __ ] look at
that is a yellow one the yellow baby
even has his ass in the blue ones face
look look at that gay [ __ ] like I'm know
any fingers but everybody knows that I
created Bionic and I'm the one that made
the colors blue and yellow
look look like [ __ ] lovers now yeah I
will show you something with all of them
with all yes all eight of them how many
kids do I have my videos here we go here
we go look at this look at look the this
is like the sock Underground cast up in
this [ __ ] like right foot first of all
we got Sonic the Hedgehog the blue one
right here and like a yellow like swing
set you up in the bottle B or some [ __ ]
Kazumi he's I guess [ __ ] then over here
we got Knuckles Knuckles the [ __ ]
Aquino red behind him we got Queen
Aleena who's purple up here on this
seesaw some [ __ ] we got the green one
Manic over here looking at him we got
the pink one selling you the Hedgehog
then Bo her we got the orange one
clearly supposed to be Mindy Latour cuz
she has orange hair [ __ ] and look
look at this that blue the why would you
need to blows you've got a lot of blue
and dark blue this can only be this can
only make sense if they are ripping off
my [ __ ] light blue Funko Chuck Dabu [ __ ]
that hog then of course we got Barbie
the yellow on over here
Sleeting and dreaming songs but shakes
and look at this I mean look at look at
that he's like on swings and [ __ ] look a
look at that look Sonic Manic Sonia the
green pink and blue ones are even the
ones up front this this looks like this
on say yeah these are the main ones like
the [ __ ] triplets oh my God see look
at this song Max oh yeah oh that is cute
that I gotta admit that's a little look
about it but just cover these two up but
I don't see those have butt sacks like
like I know I'm hating on them but damn
like that to me that is socking bottle
of me like I want to see these two I
wanna see the yellow I want to see the
yellow to D Toby
banging the blue tibi tubby in the ass I
think that the yellow one zombie pump it
what I don't know is um beep um be the
yellow one all this wiki accessories are
good but if you like go to the stores
you go look at the [ __ ] toys and [ __ ]
they're all the say the same thing the
yellow one the yellow one is a boy he's
a boy he would he is gay for the blue
one he is gay bar
yeah his name is Bob the blue one the
blue one and the yellow and have [ __ ]
bought sex you can't check anyone yeah I
wanna go see some [ __ ] there was another
one that deal is a picture of the blue
one that I really want to show you
[ __ ] I can't find it now that is cute
look a bad guy I don't want to spank his
I don't him to spank right now I can't
find it look at that oh my God oh my God
look at that look at that butt cheek
yeah that's a [ __ ] but shape
oh my oh my God there is a butt cheek
you can't make you can't make that look
at that
that's a [ __ ] but she I didn't even
add this picture [ __ ] this is on the
official Teletubbies wiki page oh my God
danceable up and dissolve it all that
that is key uh he's near by science
there's Queen Lena and Queen Lena and
Sonya of the whole oh yeah anyways this
is picture I can't find it now called
the blue lover like and everybody knows
what to I can talk about me I called
them the lovers like I pretty much
copyrighted I come and [ __ ] the lovers
so everybody knows whenever I say the
lovers they know I'm talking talking
bout because they love each other and
[ __ ]